Guide to the Geoffrey T. Hellman Papers MSS.050
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series 1: Talk of the Town
  - Y,Z, 1946-1968; 31142040613856 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Notes and Comments, 1937-1949; 31142040613856 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Notes and Comments, 1950-1967; 31142040613856 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Series 2: Profiles
  - Achelis, Elisabeth, 1939-1954; 31142040613864 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Angell, James Roland, 1933-1935; 31142040613864 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Arnold, Stanley N., 1960; 31142040613864 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Avinoff, Andrey, 1943-1948; 31142040613864 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Battle, George Gordon, 1933-1938; 31142040613864 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Biddle, George, 1933-1969; 31142040613864 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Blair, Dr. Bruce, 1938; 31142040613864 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Borge, Victor, 1953-1965; 31142040613864 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Capra, Frank, 1938-1940; 31142040613864 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Cerf, Bennett Final Draft, undated; 31142040613864 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Cerf, Bennett Research Material, 1934-1959; 31142040613864 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Cerf, Bennett Notes, undated; 31142040613864 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Cerf, Bennett Drafts, undated; 31142040613864 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Cerf, Bennett Notes by William Shawn, undated; 31142040613872 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Cerf, Bennett Correspondence and Reviews, 1941-1960; 31142040613872 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Cerf, Bennett Casual, 1961; 31142040613872 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Countess Mara, Inc., 1947-1964; 31142040613872 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Craig, John C., 1939; 31142040613872 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Crane, Joe, 1932; 31142040613872 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Cullman, Howard, 1945-1949; 31142040613872 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - D'Harnoncourt, Rene, 1958-1968; 31142040613872 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Dale, Chester Published articles, undated; 31142040613872 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Dale, Chester Source Material, 1921-1958; 31142040613872 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Dale, Chester Notes and Drafts, undated; 31142040613872 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Dale, Chester Correspondence, 1956-1958; 31142040613872 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Day, Joseph, 1925-1933; 31142040613872 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Donon, Joseph, 1954-1962; 31142040613872 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Fairchild, Sherman Mills, 1941-1967; 31142040613880 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Fish, Hamilton Jr., 1933-1968; 31142040613880 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Gallatin, Albert E., 1933-1986; 31142040613880 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Geddes, Norman Bel, 1934-1951; 31142040613880 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Glanz, Aminadov, 1946-1962; 31142040613880 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Gutherie, Dr. William Norman, 1931; 31142040613880 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Hammer, Armand, 1933-1941; 31142040613880 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Hewitt, Edward Ringwood, 1933-1940; 31142040613880 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Jones, Bassett, 1939-1960; 31142040613880 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Ketcham, Howard, 1952-1967; 31142040613880 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Knopf, Alfred A. Final Draft of Profile Parts: I, II, III, and a magazine. Copy of Part II, 1948; 31142040613880 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Knopf, Alfred A. Notes and Research, 1927-1953; 31142040613880 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Knopf, Alfred Research Publications, 1917-1947; 31142040613880 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Knopf, Alfred Early Drafts, undated; 31142040613898 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Knopf, Alfred Correspondence and Reviews, 1940-1967; 31142040613898 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Latham, Natalie Wales, 1941; 31142040613898 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Le Corbusier, Galleys and Final Version, 1947; 31142040613898 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Le Corbusier, Research Material, 1935-1947; 31142040613898 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Le Corbusier, Drafts, undated; 31142040613898 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Leterman, Elmer, 1939-1960; 31142040613898 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - McNamee, Graham, 1930; 31142040613898 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art Final Copy and Galleys, 1940; 31142040613898 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art Research and Notes, 1928-1937; 31142040613906 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art Drafts, 1969; 31142040613906 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art Correspondence, "Talk of the Town" pieces, and Finances, undated; 31142040613906 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Munn, Orson T., 1938-1940; 31142040613906 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Nessler, Charles, 1932-1933; 31142040613906 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Odlum, Floyd, 1933; 31142040613906 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Phillippe, Claudius Charles, 1954-1961; 31142040613906 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Phillippe, Claudius Charles Research Material, 1905-1954; 31142040613906 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Plimpton, Francis T. P. Galleys, 1971; 31142040613906 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Plimpton, Francis T. P. Interviews, undated; 31142040613906 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Plimpton, Francis T. P. Research Material and Notes, 1957-1971; 31142040613914 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Plimpton, Francis T. P. Draft, undated; 31142040613914 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Plimpton, Francis T. P. Correspondence and Finances, 1970; 31142040613914 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Powers, Bertram A. Galleys, 1969; 31142040613914 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Powers, Bertram A. Notes, undated; 31142040613914 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Powers, Bertram A. Research and Correspondence, 1963-1967; 31142040613914 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Powers, Bertram A. Drafts, undated; 31142040613914 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Research, 1969; 31142040613914 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Restaurant Associates Final Manuscript and Correspondence, 1964-1965; 31142040613914 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Restaurant Associates Drafts, 1964; 31142040613922 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Restaurant Associates Notes and Research Material, 1957-1964; 31142040613922 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Ripley, Dillon, 1949-1968; 31142040613922 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Ripley, Dillon Correspondence, 1946-1967; 31142040613922 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Ripley, Robert L., 1940-1960; 31142040613922 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Rivera, Diego, 1933; 31142040613922 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Robinson, Frederick B., 1932-1933; 31142040613922 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1940-1969; 31142040613922 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Schiff, Dorothy Published Version, 1968; 31142040613922 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Schiff, Dorothy Research Material, 1951-1968; 31142040613922 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Schiff, Dorothy Notes, undated; 31142040613922 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Schiff, Dorothy Early Drafts, undated; 31142040613922 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Schiff, Dorothy Original Typescript and Proofs, 1968; 31142040613930 (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - Schiff, Dorothy Correspondence, 1954-1969; 31142040613930 (Box 19, Folder 82)
  - Service, Robert, 1897-1954; 31142040613930 (Box 19, Folder 83)
  - Sikorsky, Igor, 1935-1940; 31142040613930 (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - Simon and Schuster, 1939-1963; 31142040613930 (Box 19, Folder 85)
  - Sonnenberg. Benjamin, 1936-1959; 31142040613930 (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - Speyer, James, 1932; 31142040613930 (Box 19, Folder 87)
  - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs Published Version, 1969; 31142040613948 (Box 20, Folder 88)
  - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs Research Material, 1953-1969; 31142040613948 (Box 20, Folder 89)
  - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs Research Publications, 1963-1968; 31142040613948 (Box 20, Folder 90)
  - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs Notes, undated; 31142040613948 (Box 20, Folder 91)
  - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs Early Drafts, undated; 31142040613948 (Box 20, Folder 92)
  - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs Edited Proofs and Finances, 1968-1969; 31142040613948 (Box 20, Folder 93)
  - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs Correspondence and Reviews, 1947-1969; 31142040613948 (Box 20, Folder 94)
  - Swift, J. Otis, 1932-1941; 31142040613948 (Box 20, Folder 95)
  - Todd, John R., 1936; 31142040613948 (Box 20, Folder 96)
  - Turck, Fenton B., 1938; 31142040613948 (Box 20, Folder 97)
  - Whelan, Grover, 1939-1951; 31142040613948 (Box 20, Folder 98)
  - Whitney, Cornelius Vanderbilt, 1941; 31142040613948 (Box 20, Folder 99)
  - Winlock, Herbert E. (See also - Metropolitan 1933, 1938 Museum), 1920-1930; 31142040613948 (Box 20, Folder 100)
  - Wise, Rabbi Stephen S., 1931-1933; 31142040613948 (Box 20, Folder 101)
- Series 3: Subject Category
  - American Museum of Natural History Index to Articles by Hellman, undated; 31142040613955 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - American Museum of Natural History Research Material Regarding Museum's Founding, 1864-1967; 31142040613955 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - American Museum of Natural History Research Material, 1872-1964; 31142040613955 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - American Museum of Natural History Research Material Henry Fairfield Osborn, 1917-1933; 31142040613955 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - American Museum of Natural History Research Material Margaret Mead, 1941-1967; 31142040613955 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - American Museum of Natural History Research Material Theft of Gems, 1964-1967; 31142040613955 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - American Museum of Natural History Research Material, 1965-1968; 31142040613955 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - American Museum of Natural History Research Publications, 1902-1945; 31142040613955 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - American Museum of Natural History Research Publications, 1950-1966; 31142040613955 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - American Museum of Natural History Publications Curator, 1964-1965; 31142040613955 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - American Museum of Natural History Publications Curator, 1965-1966; 31142040613955 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - American Museum of Natural History Research Publications, 1965; 31142040613963 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - American Museum of Natural History Research Publications, 1968; 31142040613963 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - American Museum of Natural History Annual Reports, 1929-1930; 31142040613963 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - American Museum of Natural History Annual Reports, 1955-1958; 31142040613963 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - American Museum of Natural History Annual Reports, 1958-1961; 31142040613963 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - American Museum of Natural History Annual Reports, 1961-1965; 31142040613963 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - American Museum of Natural History Annual Reports, 1966-1967; 31142040613963 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - American Museum of Natural History Notes from Annual Reports, undated; 31142040613963 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - American Museum of Natural History, undated; 31142040613971 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - American Museum of Natural History Talk of the Town A-L, 1946-1968; 31142040613971 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - American Museum of Natural History Talk of the Town M-Z, 1948-1968; 31142040613971 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - American Museum of Natural History Talk of the Town Museum Centennial, 1969; 31142040613971 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - American Museum of Natural History Photographs from The Hall of Man Exhibit (See Turnbull, Colin), 1968; 31142040613971 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - American Museum of Natural History Talk of the Town Wiley, Farida A., 1949-1967; 31142040613971 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - American Museum of Natural History Profile Chapman, Frank M., 1917-1964; 31142040613971 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - American Museum of Natural History Profile Chapman, Frank M. Scrapbook, 1933-1934; 31142040613971 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - American Museum of Natural History Profile Delacour, Jean, 1946-1965; 31142040613971 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - American Museum of Natural History Onward and Upward with the Arts; Final Copy, Correspondence, and Finances, 1964; 31142040613971 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - American Museum of Natural Undated History Onward and Upward with the Arts Notes, 31142040613989 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - American Museum of Natural Undated History Onward and Upward with the Arts Draft, 31142040613989 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - American Museum of Natural History Onward and Upward with the Arts Edited Proofs, 1964; 31142040613989 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - American Museum of Natural History Profile The American Museum Final Copy, 1968; 31142040613989 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - American Museum of Natural History Profile The American Museum Galleys, 1967; 31142040613989 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - American Museum of Natural History Profile The American Museum Galleys with Lawyer's Queries, 1967; 31142040613989 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - American Museum of Natural History Profile The American Museum Finances and Correspondence, 1967-1969; 31142040613989 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - American Museum of Natural Undated History Books: Bankers Bones and Beetles Index, 31142040613989 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - American Museum of Natural History Books: Bankers Bones and Beetles Manuscript pages 1-199, 1968; 31142040613989 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - American Museum of Natural History Books: Bankers Bones and Beetles Manuscript pages 200-361, 1968; 31142040613989 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - American Museum of Natural Undated History Books: Bankers Bones and Beetles Edited Chapters, 31142040613989 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - American Museum of Natural History Books: Bankers Bones and Beetles Captions for Illustrations, undated; 31142040613989 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - American Museum of Natural History Books: Bankers Bones and Beetles Legal Documents, 1965; 31142040613989 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - American Museum of Natural History Books: Bankers Bones and Beetles Correspondence, 1968; 31142040613997 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - American Museum of Natural History Books: Bankers Bones and Beetles Book Reviews, 1968-1969; 31142040613997 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Calder, Alexander Profile, 1941; 31142040613997 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Calder, Alexander Research, Correspondence and Talk of the Town, 1929-1969; 31142040613997 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Calder, Alexander Onward and Upward With The Arts, 1960; 31142040613997 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Cooper Union Profile, 1937-1938; 31142040613997 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Cooper Union A Reporter At Large, 1938; 31142040613997 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Cooper Union Talk of the Town, 1946; 31142040613997 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Crowninshield, Frank Profile, 1942; 31142040613997 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Crowninshield, Frank Profile Notes and Source Material, 1891-1942; 31142040613997 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Crowninshield, Frank Profile Correspondence, 1941-1947; 31142040613997 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Crowninshield, Frank That Was New York, 1889-1966; 31142040614003 (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - Crowninshield, Frank "Vanity Fair-A" Play by Geoffrey Hellman, 1961-1967; 31142040614003 (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - Crowninshield, Frank Press Clippings, 1915-1947; 31142040614003 (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Bloomingdale, Samuel J., 1963-1964; 31142040614003 (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Guggenheim, 1953-1959; 31142040614003 (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Guggenheim Museum, 1945-1963; 31142040614003 (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Lehman, Arthur, 1955-1956; 31142040614003 (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Lewisohn, 1929-1958; 31142040614003 (Box 29, Folder 61)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Ryan, 1954-1955; 31142040614003 (Box 29, Folder 62)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Schiff-Warburg Published Article, Notes and Drafts, 1955; 31142040614003 (Box 29, Folder 63)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Schiff-Warburg Research, 1946-1954; 31142040614003 (Box 29, Folder 64)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Schiff-Warburg Correspondence, 1933-1958; 31142040614003 (Box 29, Folder 65)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Seligman, Adrian, 1938-1968; 31142040614003 (Box 29, Folder 66)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Seligman Drafts, 1954; 31142040616016 (Box 30, Folder 67)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Seligman Research Material, 1880-1969; 31142040616016 (Box 30, Folder 68)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Seligman Correspondence, 1953-1955; 31142040616016 (Box 30, Folder 69)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Straus(s), 1932-1969; 31142040616016 (Box 30, Folder 70)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Our Crowd by Stephen Birmingham, 1965-1967; 31142040616016 (Box 30, Folder 71)
  - Jewish Dynastic Families Correspondence, 1954-1966; 31142040616016 (Box 30, Folder 72)
  - Lewis, Wilmarth S. Profiles Final Copy and Edited draft, 1949; 31142040616016 (Box 30, Folder 73)
  - Lewis, Wilmarth S. Undated Profiles Edited Draft, 31142040616016 (Box 30, Folder 74)
  - Lewis, Wilmarth S. Profiles Notes and Sources, 1948-1949; 31142040616016 (Box 30, Folder 75)
  - Lewis, Wilmarth S. Profiles Correspondence, 1948-1969; 31142040616016 (Box 30, Folder 76)
  - Lewis, Wilmarth S. Onward And Upward With The Arts, 1940-1958; 31142040616016 (Box 30, Folder 77)
  - New York Botanical Gardens List of Articles, undated; 31142040616024 (Box 31, Folder 78)
  - New York Botanical Gardens Talk of the Town, 1945-1967; 31142040616024 (Box 31, Folder 79)
  - New York Botanical Gardens Robbins, William J. Profile, 1943-1951; 31142040616024 (Box 31, Folder 80)
  - New York Botanical Gardens Onward and Upward with the Sciences, 1963-1964; 31142040616024 (Box 31, Folder 81)
  - New York Botanical Gardens Onward and Upward with the Sciences, 1966; 31142040616024 (Box 31, Folder 82)
  - New York Botanical Gardens Symposium, 1968; 31142040616024 (Box 31, Folder 83)
  - New York Botanical Gardens Correspondence, 1960-1968; 31142040616024 (Box 31, Folder 84)
  - New York Botanical Gardens Publications, 1903-1967; 31142040616024 (Box 31, Folder 85)
  - New York Botanical Gardens Publications, 1967-1968; 31142040616024 (Box 31, Folder 86)
  - Smithsonian Institution Research Material, 1842-1969; 31142040616032 (Box 32, Folder 87)
  - Smithsonian Institution Research Material, 1967-1969; 31142040616032 (Box 32, Folder 88)
  - Smithsonian Institution Legislative History, 1846-1965; 31142040616032 (Box 32, Folder 89)
  - Smithsonian Institution Legal History, 1898-1965; 31142040616032 (Box 32, Folder 90)
  - Smithsonian Institution Research Publications, 1947-1959; 31142040616032 (Box 32, Folder 91)
  - Smithsonian Institution Research Publications, 1962-1966; 31142040616032 (Box 32, Folder 92)
  - Smithsonian Institution Magazine Articles about Smithsonian Institution, 1854-1964; 31142040616032 (Box 32, Folder 93)
  - Smithsonian Institution Magazine Articles about Smithsonian Institution, 1964-1966; 31142040616040 (Box 33, Folder 94)
  - Smithsonian Institution Press Releases, 1961-1969; 31142040616040 (Box 33, Folder 95)
  - Smithsonian Institution Newspaper Clippings, undated; 31142040616040 (Box 33, Folder 96)
  - Smithsonian Institution Interoffice Memoranda, 1964-1965; 31142040616040 (Box 33, Folder 97)
  - Smithsonian Institution Photocopies of Mail Received by Smithsonian, 1956-1964; 31142040616040 (Box 33, Folder 98)
  - Smithsonian Institution Carmichael, Leonard, 1964-1965; 31142040616040 (Box 33, Folder 99)
  - Smithsonian Institution Evans, Clifford and Meggers, Betty, 1962; 31142040616040 (Box 33, Folder 100)
  - Smithsonian Institution Freer Gallery of Art, 1928-1964; 31142040616040 (Box 33, Folder 101)
  - Smithsonian Institution Henry, Joseph, 1965; 31142040616040 (Box 33, Folder 102)
  - Smithsonian Institution Hirshhorn, Joseph H., 1964-1966; 31142040616040 (Box 33, Folder 103)
  - Smithsonian Institution Hornaday, William T., 1890-1957; 31142040616040 (Box 33, Folder 104)
  - Smithsonian Institution Langley, Samuel P. Airplane Controversy, 1896-1928; 31142040616040 (Box 33, Folder 105)
  - Smithsonian Institution National Collection of Fine Arts, 1964; 31142040616040 (Box 33, Folder 106)
  - Smithsonian Institution National Portrait Gallery, 1968; 31142040616057 (Box 34, Folder 107)
  - Smithsonian Institution Osborn, Henry F., 1906-1907; 31142040616057 (Box 34, Folder 108)
  - Smithsonian Institution Ripley, S. Dillon, 1964-1968; 31142040616057 (Box 34, Folder 109)
  - Smithsonian Institution Ritterbush, Phillip C. 1964, 1964-1968; 31142040616057 (Box 34, Folder 110)
  - Smithsonian Institution Sarcophagus of the Roman Emperor Alexander Severus, 1857-1965; 31142040616057 (Box 34, Folder 111)
  - Smithsonian Institution Bicentennial Celebration, 1965; 31142040616057 (Box 34, Folder 112)
  - Smithsonian Institution Bicentennial Celebration Invitations, 1965; 31142040616057 (Box 34, Folder 113)
  - Smithsonian Institution Bicentennial Celebration Press Releases and Newspaper clippings, 1965; 31142040616057 (Box 34, Folder 114)
  - Smithsonian Institution Events, 1964-1967; 31142040616057 (Box 34, Folder 115)
  - Smithsonian Institution Smithsonian Events, undated; 31142040616057 (Box 34, Folder 116)
  - Smithsonian Institution Notes Covering, 1838-1897; 31142040616057 (Box 34, Folder 117)
  - Smithsonian Institution Notes Covering, 1898-19651; 31142040616065 (Box 35, Folder 118)
  - Smithsonian Institution Notes, undated; 31142040616065 (Box 35, Folder 119)
  - Smithsonian Institution Casual, 1945-1953; 31142040616065 (Box 35, Folder 120)
  - Smithsonian Institution "Talk of the Town", 1949-1960; 31142040616065 (Box 35, Folder 121)
  - Smithsonian Institution Profile Part I Galley Proof, 1966; 31142040616065 (Box 35, Folder 122)
  - Smithsonian Institution Profile Part II Galley Proof, 1966; 31142040616065 (Box 35, Folder 123)
  - Smithsonian Institution Profile Part III Galley Proof, 1966; 31142040616065 (Box 35, Folder 124)
  - Smithsonian Institution Profile Magazine Tearsheets, 1966; 31142040616065 (Box 35, Folder 125)
  - Smithsonian Institution Profile Correspndence and Expenses, 1965-1968; 31142040616065 (Box 35, Folder 126)
  - Smithsonian Institution Octopus on the Mall Business Correspondence, 1964-1967; 31142040616065 (Box 35, Folder 127)
  - Smithsonian Institution Octopus on the Mall Early Draft, undated; 31142040616065 (Box 35, Folder 128)
  - Smithsonian Institution Octopus on the Mall Draft submitted to Lippincott pg. 1-99, 1966; 31142040616065 (Box 35, Folder 129)
  - Smithsonian Institution Octopus on the Mall Draft submitted to Lippincott pg. 100-197, 1966; 31142040616073 (Box 36, Folder 130)
  - Smithsonian Institution Octopus on the Mall Draft submitted to Reynolds pg. 1-99, 1967; 31142040616073 (Box 36, Folder 131)
  - Smithsonian Institution Octopus on the Mall Draft submitted to Reynolds pg. 100-197, 1967; 31142040616073 (Box 36, Folder 132)
  - Smithsonian Collection 1966 Octopus on the Mall Author's Original Manuscript pgs. 1-111, undated; 31142040616073 (Box 36, Folder 133)
  - Smithsonian Collection Octopus on the Mall Author's Original Manuscript pgs. 112-222, 1966; 31142040616073 (Box 36, Folder 134)
  - Smithsonian Collection Octopus on the Mall Author's Original Manuscript pgs. 223-333, 1966; 31142040616073 (Box 36, Folder 135)
  - Smithsonian Collection Octopus on the Mall Author's Original Manuscript pgs. 334-444, 1966; 31142040616073 (Box 36, Folder 136)
  - Smithsonian Collection Octopus on the Mall Author's Original Manuscript pgs. 445-554, 1966; 31142040616073 (Box 36, Folder 137)
  - Smithsonian Collection Octopus on the Mall Typescript Copy pgs. 1-115, 1966; 31142040616081 (Box 37, Folder 138)
  - Smithsonian Collection Octopus on the Mall Typescript Copy pgs. 116-230, 1966; 31142040616081 (Box 37, Folder 139)
  - Smithsonian Collection Octopus on the Mall Typescript Copy pgs. 231-345, 1966; 31142040616081 (Box 37, Folder 140)
  - Smithsonian Collection Octopus on the Mall Typescript Copy pgs. 346-460, 1966; 31142040616081 (Box 37, Folder 141)
  - Smithsonian Collection Octopus on the Mall Typescript Copy pgs. 461-575, 1966; 31142040616081 (Box 37, Folder 142)
  - Smithsonian Collection Octopus on the Mall Typescript Copy pgs. 576-693, 1966; 31142040616081 (Box 37, Folder 143)
  - Smithsonian Collection Octopus on the Mall Advertisements, 1967; 31142040616081 (Box 37, Folder 144)
  - Smithsonian Collection Octopus on the Mall Book Reviews, 1967-1968; 31142040616081 (Box 37, Folder 145)
  - Smithsonian Collection Octopus on the Mall Correspondence, 1965-1968; 31142040616081 (Box 37, Folder 146)
- Series 4: Casuals
  - Note from Hellman, 1969; 31142040616099 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - A, 1941-1960; 31142040616099 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - B, C, D, 1940-1960; 31142040616099 (Box 40, Folder 3)